animelab.com 2017-07-18

# AnimeLab - Privacy Policy

### Your Information

When referring to 'personal information', we mean information which identifies you as an individual or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your name or pseudonym, your postal address or email address and/or your phone number are examples of personal information.

### Information Collected

The only information that we collect about you when you use AnimeLab is what you tell us about yourself, for example, when you submit feedback to us and provide your name or pseudonym and email address or other personal details. If you receive email communications from us, you will always have the opportunity to unsubscribe from receiving such emails.

In common with many websites, when you read, browse or download information from our website, we or our internet service provider may also collect information such as the date and time of your visit to the website, the pages accessed and any information downloaded. This information is used for statistical, reporting and website administration, maintenance and improvement purposes only.

Like many websites, our Website may use 'cookies' from time to time. Cookies are small text files that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser. Cookies may also be used to record non-personal information such as the date, time or duration of your visit, or the pages accessed, for website administration, statistical and maintenance purposes. Any such information will be aggregated and not linked to particular individuals. The default settings of browsers like Internet Explorer always allow cookies, but users can easily erase cookies from their hard-drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please note that some parts of the Website may not function fully for users that disallow cookies.

### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

We may collect, use and exchange your information so that we can: 

  * establish your identity and assess applications for products and services;
  * communicate with you on all things anime;
  * email you e-newsletters or other updates (if you have requested to receive them). If you decide that you no longer want to receive such updates from us, you will have the ability to unsubscribe; and
  * conduct and improve AnimeLab and improve the user experience.

This is not an exhaustive list. We may also collect, use and exchange your information in other ways where permitted or required by law. 

### Direct Marketing

We may also use your information so that we can promote and market anime, services and special offers that we think will be of interest to you. This marketing may be carried out in a variety of ways (including by email, SMS/MMS, or social media or by customising online content and displaying advertising on websites and may continue until you unsubscribe or contact [answers@animelab.com](mailto:answers@animelab.com) to opt out.

### Performance and Remarketing Cookies

Partners who help us serve advertising on and off the Website and analytics companies may also put cookies on your device. We use several third-party vendors to help deliver ads for relevant AnimeLab products and services to you when you visit certain pages on our Website and then visit certain third-party sites. We may share with third-party ad partners an anonymous, common account identifier (such as a unique ID), to help us measure and tailor ads and services provided to you. Below is information about one such vendor. Please note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies and does not include use of cookies by any third parties. 

  * Google Analytics

AnimeLab uses a specific cookie in order to facilitate the use of Google Universal Analytics for users logged-in to the Applications or the Platforms (“Logged-In User). If you are a Logged-In User, AnimeLab may use your AnimeLab user ID in combination with Google Universal Analytics and Google Analytics to track and analyze the pages of the Services you visit. We do this only to better understand how you use the Website and the other Services, with a view to offering improvements for all AnimeLab users; and to tailor our business and marketing activities accordingly, both generally and specifically to you. Google Analytics cookies do not provide AnimeLab with any Personal Information. 

[Learn more about privacy at Google and to opt-out of this feature by installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)

  * Google Display Advertising

Additionally, AnimeLab uses Google Analytics code that allows for certain forms of display advertising and other advanced features. Subject to change, the Google Display Advertising features AnimeLab currently uses are Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager Integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. 

These features are used to advertise online; to allow third-party vendors, including Google, to show you advertising across the Internet; to allow AnimeLab and third-party vendors, including Google, to use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to the Website and to report how ad impressions, uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to the Website. Data from Google's interest-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) is also combined with Google Analytics to better understand the needs of AnimeLab users and to improve the Services. 

You may opt out of such display advertising at any time by visiting your [Google Ads Settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or by installing and running the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

### Security of Personal Information

Irrespective of whether personal information is stored electronically or in hard copy form, we take reasonable steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

We keep your hard-copy or electronic records on our premises and systems or offsite using trusted third parties. Our security safeguards include: 

  * training and reminding our staff of their obligations with regard to your information;
  * when we send information overseas, or use third parties that handle or store data, we ensure that appropriate data handling and security arrangements are in place; and
  * where practical, we keep information only for as long as required.

### Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information

To make a request to access or correct any personal information we hold about you, please contact: us via email at [answers@animelab.com](mailto:answers@animelab.com).

Please provide us with as much detail as you can about the particular information you seek, in order to help us retrieve it. An access fee may be charged where permitted by law. In certain circumstances, we may not be required by law to provide you with access or to correct your personal information. If that is the case, we will give you our reasons for that decision.

We take reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

### Further Information

AnimeLab may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of those sites.

We may need to change this Policy. If we do, we will post the updated version on AnimeLab. Please also note that during the course of our relationship with you, we may tell you more about how we handle your information.

### Making a Privacy Complaint

You may contact us at [answers@animelab.com](mailto:answers@animelab.com) to notify us of any privacy complaint you have against us, including if you think we have failed to comply with the Australian Privacy Principles. You may also lodge a complaint with a relevant regulator such as the Australian Information Commissioner via www.oaic.gov.au.
